<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Danny Yagan | UC Berkeley Economics on Danny Yagan</title>
    <link>https://dyagan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Danny Yagan | UC Berkeley Economics on Danny Yagan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dyagan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Yagan - About</title>
      <link>https://dyagan.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dyagan.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum vitae.
Danny Yagan is Assistant Professor of Economics at the University of California-Berkeley, Faculty Research Fellow of the National Bureau of Economic Research, and Faculty Director of the Taxation and Inequality Initiative of the Berkeley Opportunity Lab.
His research uses large datasets and natural experiments to study U.S. tax policy, business investment, income inequality, upward mobility, and recession recovery. In 2018 he was awarded a Sloan Foundation Research Fellowship for early-career contributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Yagan - Mobility Report Cards</title>
      <link>https://dyagan.github.io/projects/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dyagan.github.io/projects/college/</guid>
      <description>Mobility Report Cards for All 2,199 U.S. Colleges Constructed using our publicly available data from: &amp;ldquo;Mobility Report Cards: The Role of Colleges in Intergenerational Mobility&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; (with R. Chetty, J. N. Friedman, E. Saez, and N. Turner). Manuscript (January 2017), non-technical summary, slides, study website, data, NYT data tool, and presscoverage. --
ASA Institute Of Business &amp;amp; Computer Technology ASU And Northern Arizona U And U Of Arizona Abilene Christian University Abraham Baldwin Agricultural College Academy Of Art University Adams State University Adelphi University Adirondack Community College - SUNY Adrian College Advanced Institute Of Hair Design Advanced Technology Institute Adventist University of Health Sciences Agnes Scott College Aiken Technical College Alabama Agricultural &amp;amp; Mechanical University Alabama Southern Community College Alamance Community College Alamo Community College District Albany College Of Pharmacy And Health Sciences Albany State University Albany Technical College Albertus Magnus College Albion College Albright College Alderson Broaddus University Alfred University Allan Hancock College Allegany College Of Maryland Allegheny College Allen County Community College Alma College Alpena Community College Altamaha Technical College Alvernia University Alverno College Alvin Community College Amarillo College American Career College of Los Angeles CA American Institute Of Business American Intercontinental University American International College American Musical &amp;amp; Dramatic Academy American National University American University  Amherst College Ancilla Domini College Anderson University of Anderson IN Anderson University of Anderson SC Andrews University Angelina College Angelo State University Anna Maria College Anne Arundel Community College Antelope Valley College Anthem College And The Bryman School Of Arizona Anthem Institute Antonelli College Appalachian State University Aquinas College Arapahoe Community College Arcadia University Argosy University Arizona Western College Arkansas Northeastern College Arkansas State University Arkansas State University - Beebe Arkansas Tech University Armstrong Atlantic State University Art Center College Of Design Art Institute Of Colorado  Art Institute Of Fort Lauderdale  Art Institute Of Houston  Art Institute Of New York City  Art Institute Of Philadelphia  Art Institute Of Phoenix  Art Institute Of Pittsburgh  Art Institute Of Portland  Art Institute Of Seattle  Art Institute Of York - Pennsylvania Art Institutes International Minnesota  Asbury College Asheville Buncombe Technical Community College Ashland University Asnuntuck Community College Assumption College Athens Technical College Atlanta Metropolitan State College Atlanta Technical College Atlantic Cape Community College Auburn University Auburn University Montgomery Augsburg College Augusta Technical College Augustana College of Rock Island IL Augustana College of Sioux Falls SD Aurora University Austin College Austin Community College Austin Peay State University Automotive Training Center Aveda Institute Aveda Institute Covington Averett University Avila University Azusa Pacific University Babson College Bainbridge State College Baker College Baker University Baldwin Wallace University Ball State University Baltimore School Of Massage Baptist Bible College Baptist Bible College Of Pennsylvania Bard College Barnard College Barry University Barstow Community College Barton College Barton County Community College Bates College Bates Technical College Bay De Noc Community College Bay Path College Bay State College Baylor University Beaufort County Community College Becker College Bel - Rea Institute Of Animal Technology Belhaven University Bellarmine University Bellevue College Bellevue University Bellingham Technical College Belmont Abbey College Belmont College Belmont University Beloit College Benedictine College Benedictine University Bennett College Bennington College Bentley University Bergen Community College Berkeley College of New York NY Berkeley College of Woodland Park NJ Berklee College Of Music Berkshire Community College Berry College Beth Medrash Govoha Of America Bethany College of Bethany WV Bethany College of Lindsborg KS Bethany Lutheran College Bethel College Bethel University of McKenzie TN Bethel University of Saint Paul MN Bethune Cookman University Bevill State Community College Big Bend Community College Binghamton University Biola University Birmingham Southern College Bishop State Community College Bismarck State College Black Hawk College Black River Technical College Blackburn University Blackhawk Technical College Bladen Community College Blinn College Bloomfield College Bloomsburg University of Pennsylvania Blue Mountain Community College Blue Ridge Community College of Flat Rock NC Blue Ridge Community College of Weyers Cave VA Bluefield State College Bluffton University Boise State University Boricua College Bossier Parish Community College Boston College Boston University Bowdoin College Bowling Green State University Bradford School of Columbus OH Bradford School of Pittsburgh PA Bradley University Brandeis University Brazosport College Brenau University Brevard College Brewton Parker College Briar Cliff University Briarcliffe College Bridgerland Applied Technology College Bridgewater College Bridgewater State University Brigham Young University Brigham Young University - Hawaii Brigham Young University-Idaho Bristol Community College Brookdale Community College Brookline College Brooks Institute Broome Community College Broward College Brown College Brown University Brunswick Community College Bryan College Bryant University Bryn Mawr College Bucknell University Bucks County Community College Buena Vista University Bunker Hill Community College Burlington County College - Pemberton Campus Butler County Community College of Butler PA Butler County Community College of El Dorado KS Butler University Butte College CSU Bakersfield CSU Chico CSU Dominguez Hills CSU East Bay CSU Fresno CSU Fullerton CSU Long Beach CSU Los Angeles CSU Monterey Bay CSU Northridge CSU San Bernardino CSU San Marcos CSU Stanislaus CUNY Bernard M.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>